Welcome into the lounge presented by
DraftKings. I'm Ryan Mink here with
Garrett Downing and we are thrilled to
sit down with quarterback Cheeto Auzier,
fresh off resigning a one-year deal. And
Cheeto, we'll start here. According to
reports, you signed for $5. So, thank
you for signing such a team friendly
deal. We really appreciate it.
>> Yeah, know it's for the love of the
game. And you know, everybody always
says, you know, I'll play football for
free and do this, you know, but I'm
actually showing it that I will. So, $5
that, you know, they actually gave me a
uh they tried to get me a McDonald's
upstairs. They gave me the hot and spicy
McChick, but they got me uh I think a
McMuffin.
>> Okay.
>> I said, I'm going to need another $5,
you know, hot spicy.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> So, viewers and listeners know. So, this
was uh Jeff Zbeck, our our friend at the
Athletic, accidentally tweeted that it
was a one-year $5 instead of $5 million.
So, a little bit of a difference there.
>> A little bit. And you had a little fun
with that saying just enough to buy a
spicy McChick. Yeah.
>> So, hot and spicy McChick. So, so you
you're going to get that though
eventually here?
>> Oh, no. I'm going to get a bunch of
them. I'm I'm I'm training right now,
but I know there will be a couple cheat
days here and there. So, you know, I'll
try to tap. I know Malachi got a deal
with McDonald's. Hopefully, he can get
me some free ones. I don't have to waste
my $5. So, yeah.
>> Just to continue the McDonald's story
here for a little bit longer. Actually,
when Joe Flacco signed his record
contract back in 2013 at the time, it
was famous that he then celebrated and
went through the McDonald's drive-thru
and got, you know, something like that.
So, that's like a famous picture. So,
there you go. So, when you leave here,
there's McDonald's right by the
facility. You can see through there.
>> Say less. Say less.
>> So, Gino, just what made you want to
come back here to Baltimore?
>> Oh, man. There's just so much more to do
here. Um, obviously how we ended last
year, how I ended last year. um big chip
on my shoulder and I I could definitely
sense the energy just being here today.
You know, there's a big chip on
everybody's shoulder. Um there's
obviously new uh coaching staff. Um you
know, I think they're they're amazing so
far. Um and the guys that I met last
year on the team, you know, we built
really strong relationships. Um a lot of
young guys and you know, we're hoping to
make that next step uh for those guys
and also just as a defense and as a
room. So I'm excited to be a part of
that.
>> Yeah. What did you take away from your
first season in Baltimore?
>> Um, it was amazing. Um, even though all
the ups and downs, um, I think that we
like no one ever pointed the finger at
anybody, you know, everything was always
guided towards success, like how how do
we get over the hump? How do we, you
know, be consistent? How do we, you
know, solve issues? And even though we
weren't getting the results that we
wanted, um, that energy was there and
the guys, the leaders, everybody, you
know, played a part in that. And then
obviously um just being in the black
black purple and gold, you know, is
swaggy. You know, it felt good to be on
this side of it, you know, walking out
of the tunnel, MT Bank Stadium. Uh the
people in Baltimore are really cool.
>> Yeah, it's just it was it was an amazing
experience. Obviously, um like I said,
um we have a little taste in our mouth
just from last year, but um other than
that, you know, I think that, you know,
being able to come back here, you know,
gives us another opportunity to do
something special.
>> You you mentioned the new coaching
staff. Did you have a chance after
signing your contract to meet some of
your new coaches and just what was your
impression?
>> Oh, no. Great energy. Um, very lively, a
lot of smiles, a lot of juice. Um, could
feel it permeating through the building.
Um, obviously I was here last year with
uh Harbaugh and that coaching staff and
they were amazing too. Yeah.
>> Um, you know, but uh, you know, coach
Jesse, coach Weave, Coach Mickens,
obviously two still here. Um, you know,
a lot of these coaches, especially on
the defensive side of the ball, um, you
know, I just feel a really strong energy
and strong pull. So, I'm excited to see
how that plays out during the season.
Um, and then shout out al also the coach
Lavine, you know, becoming the special
teams coordinator. So, that's really
dope. And yeah, I just think it's very
young, very um, a lot of juice. A lot of
juice, I'll say.
>> Well, well, last year I feel like you
you were one of, if not the, you know,
best Ravens addition in the offseason.
like just that deal just really worked
out, you know, and uh what do you feel
like you proved last year about your
career that you now take into this
upcoming season? Um, I mean really I was
trying to prove to myself always, you
know, just who I am, you know, entering
last year into year nine, coming off a
couple of injuries, you know, um,
feeling good, but, you know, wanting to
put out some some tape, you know, to to
to feel good about myself and like who I
am, you know, um, I know who I am, but
at the same time, it's like I want to
show it on Sundays and Thursdays and
Mondays. So, um, just having the
opportunity, you know, when however they
came, uh, to go out there, you know,
knock the ball down, make some tackles,
do some things, you know, it was really
fun and exciting. And I think this year
it's the same thing. You know, it's not
about, um, anything other than, you
know, respect. You know, just trying to
go after respect. Um, number one,
self-respect and then, you know, gaining
respect of the opponents, gaining
respect to my teammates and coaches and
then, you know, as a team, you know,
gaining respect as a defense, as
offense, as a team, you know, all the
way up to, you know, the final goal,
which is, you know, the Super Bowl.
That's always the goal. So,
>> to his point about I thought the signing
worked out really well. You played you
played a ton of snaps. You played a lot
of big moments. You were on the field a
lot and the team really relied on you
like you you were a cornerstone piece of
this defense uh last year and coming in
which is which says a lot at that
position uh for the for to prove
yourself and be counted on in that
moment. And so as as you look at this
year and building off of what you were
able to do, what do you foresee as your
goals and expectations for how you build
upon what you did last year? Yeah, just
to be consistent, you know. I think, you
know, corner is one of the hardest
positions to be consistent, you know, um
to have like a consistent mindset, mind
frame, consistent process, consistent
technique. Um cuz the results are always
going to change. You know, you could be
in the perfect spot. These quarterbacks
and receivers, you know, they make a lot
of plays. But, you know, if you can make
more than 50% of your plays, you know,
you're you're in good business at
corner. And I think um you know, that's
kind of my goal. And then also just to
be, you know, entering year 10. I want
to be a leader, you know, to all the
guys who who rely, you know, the young
guys, any questions they have, um, on
the defense on on both sides of the
ball, whatever that may be. You know, I
just want to be a consistent person that
they can be like look at and be like,
"Okay, like let me ask Cheeto this
question because I haven't really seen
him, you know, say something and then he
he don't do it." You know what I'm
saying? I want to be that model of
consistency.
>> How did you how'd you approach Go ahead.
>> Well, I was just gonna say I thought you
were that last year. Like I I noticed
that throughout the year is that even
early on I remember being at the Michael
Phelps swimming thing and like guys just
like gravitate you to you. You you have
this kind of energy especially with the
younger corners and you have this kind
of moxy and this aura about you that um
it felt like you became a leader last
year. Nate Wiggins even told us on the
podcast that you helped him kind of
learn the process of watching film and
like he gave you a big a lot of credit
for helping him elevate his game and
kind of learn the the cerebral mental
aspect of the game too, right?
>> I mean at the end of the day this a
game, you know, so like they they would
say they say I'm a a 20-year-old trapped
in a 30-year-old body or something like
that. Like cuz you know I like to have
fun, you know, I could kick it with, you
know, any age group, whether that's 20
year olds or, you know, 50-y old, 60-y
old talking business or chilling,
whatever it is. Marlo's not that old.
>> Hell yeah. My bad. Marlo. Marlo.
My age. We the same draft class. But,
you know, um I think it's one of those
things where like, you know, we just,
you know, life's all about connection.
Life's about relationships. You want to
meet people where they're at and
hopefully they meet you where you're at.
And um yeah, I think on on the team, we
just had some really good fun times. You
know, funny. I'm just thinking about
them. I want to smile cuz it's just
funny times that we would have together.
So, um that's that's what it's about.
Football is supposed to be fun. Um so,
we definitely made it fun last year.
>> Yeah. What do you what do you see for
this secondary moving forward? You know,
now a lot of these corners are coming
back. We talk about Marlo and Nate's
coming back and other guys are coming
back. You have, you know, safeties
obviously with Kyle and Malachi and and
some new additions, but this secondary
is going to kind of largely remain the
same. How much can that benefit you
moving forward?
>> Oh, it benefits us um you know,
immensely. I think uh you know we'll see
the new kinks and everything with the
defense, but um I definitely think you
know the fact that the room has been you
know generally the same. Obviously we
lost some brothers and you know shout
out to them. They'll always make an
impact on us but it's like you know we
have to make a leap like we have to make
a leap. Um
>> you know these windows aren't open
forever and we know that how much it
matters um for us to play good as a
secondary as a defense and I think
everybody again is like on the same
page. Um, and I think like that's the
first step is like we're already
together. We're already close with each
other. Now it's just, you know, the
details of the new defense and, you
know, all the things that we want to do
differently or the same or keep the
same.
>> And then, yeah, just continue to get
grow tighter as a unit. Um, you know, I
think, you know, the team that usually
stands at the end is the closest team,
the guys who are the closest with each
other and also the most healthy. So,
those are the two things that we'll be
focusing on, I think, as a as a
secondary.
>> Yeah. Is there excitement around Jesse
Mener has been one of the best defensive
coordinators in the league the last
couple of years. Now he comes here to
Baltimore and his defense has been one
that's that's being emulated similar
system. What to what's run out in
Seattle with with Mike McDonald who of
course came up in this system as well.
So what what's your excitement level of
playing for Jesse and in this defense?
Oh,
>> I'm very excited. Um, you know, he hit
me up yesterday and then I looked at,
you know, we had actually had a text
thread before cuz, you know, I think
before I was going to come here last
year, the Chargers wanted
>> He was trying to pull you out to
>> LA. We had a little we had a little tech
I don't know if I mean I think that's
okay to share. Yeah. Um, we had a little
text thread and you know, it's like,
okay, finally, you know, get to work
together. So, you know, we had calls
back then and, you know, now being able
to work with him now, you know, it's
just like, you know, it was supposed to
happen. So, I'm excited to have like a
defensive head coach, you know,
secondary co head coach background and
all that stuff. I think it's going to be
great for our room, great for me. Um,
and I think, yeah, like everything right
now is in place to, you know, for us,
especially in the secondary, to do our
job and to hopefully get better and make
a leap. So, I'm excited for that part of
it. I know like we're not going to skip
steps. like there's going to be things
that we have to get through whether
that's adversity, dealing with success,
um anything, you know, roles changing,
whatever that may look like, but I think
we're all, you know, in it for the unit.
You know, I talked to coach Mickens
earlier and he talked about something
about unit glory, you know, and I think
that really just hit my hit my head
like, you know, it's not about your
glory, it's about the unit glory. And
obviously it's obvious, but you know, in
the NFL people have pride, ego, all
these things, but like I never felt that
with our team. I think that we're
already like that much closer to, you
know, when he implements that message,
it'll bring us that much closer to like
where we need to be. So,
>> that's awesome.
>> Now, I I don't know if people know this,
but you're a pretty avid chess player.
>> Oh, yeah. So, so who do you like to play
on the team and kind of what's your
strategy when you're playing chess and
and and how does it help you in your
game? Like, does does it help you? Do
you take that mindset when you're
playing football?
>> Yeah, chess is an amazing game. It's a
great connector. I feel like when I was
in Brazil this off seasonason, I was
playing like there was people playing
chess on the street. It's like if you're
in any country and you know how to play
chess, like you're going to find people
that you can connect with.
>> Did you play?
>> Uh I told him I would play. It was like
a dude on the corner of the street and I
was like, "Oh, we could play." And then
I walked away. Then I was that, you
know, I had to go to the beach. I went
to the beach. I went to the beach. But
it was a cool conversation at least. But
um yeah, on the team, you know, I played
uh Cross. He's one of the trainers.
>> Okay.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I'll be whipping on him.
He's beat me. He's beating me once. He's
going to be happy I said that. But he's
beat me once. Uh I've been whipping on
him mostly. But then uh other players
play, but he's the one I probably play
the most. Yeah. And then chess, you
know, chess and football, I think, you
know, just the process of everything.
You know, obviously on chess, pieces
have different points. You know, your
rook's worth five, your bishop and
knight are worth three, then your queen
is worth nine, and your king is like,
you lose your king, you lose the game.
And I feel like um you protect the
pieces based on how much they're worth.
And I think in life in football, there's
priorities. There's things you have to
get get through and and get towards. And
it's like you have to be in tune with
your most important pieces. You know
what I'm saying? So like
>> whether that's a young football player,
young basketball player, whatever they
do, you know, they want to get into the
league and then all of a sudden start
thinking about what they're going to do
after the league or start um you know,
>> I don't know doing music or something.
It's like, okay, but you want to be be
in tune with your star player. Like this
is your queen. This is your queen. Your
career is your queen. this is what got
you the opportunity. You know what I'm
saying? That may be your rook or that
may be a pawn or you know your family
might be the rook. You know, all these
different things. So, it's priorities. I
think then if you implement that in your
life, I feel like it's helped me like um
implement priorities and also pattern
recognition. You know, being able to
look at a board and be like, "Okay, I've
been in this position before. What's the
best move?" You know, on the football
field, it's like, "Oh, I've seen this
formation before. What's the uh route
concept that happened?" Or, "What's the
what's the uh possible threats and all
these things?" Like, what's the best
move to make? I think those are the two
biggest things I think um chess has
helped me in life and in football.
>> Interesting.
>> Did you grow up playing or when did you
learn and start playing?
>> I was a checkers player growing up. I
think my brother played chess mainly,
but I really started playing on the
Cowboys. Okay.
>> Um
>> like 2019 when Amari Cooper came.
>> I played in college too, but like I
really started playing when Amari Cooper
came. We used to play every day after
practice and then you know you have a
rival, you know, we're talking talking
stuff to each other and uh you know,
some great conversations too. So, um,
yeah, from there I just really started
playing a lot, you know.
>> Yeah. Speaking of past teams, do you
have any familiarity with Trey
Hendrickson?
>> That's my dog. That's my dog. Yeah, we
we we've been to the Mountaintop
together. Um, we came in the same time
to the Bengals. Um, we have a bunch of
great times hanging out. Um, yeah, we
still be texting. We have similar
interests in different things. So, um,
I'm really happy that he's here. I saw
that and I was happy. I was like, let me
hurry up
with my dog. So, um I know the the
Baltimore fans, they're going to love
Trey. You know, he's relentless. He's a
closer.
>> Um you know, he's getting 17 sacks every
season. He's been like healthy, you
know, so and he's healthy right now. And
um yeah, I'm just excited to play with
him and have, you know, a brother that
I've that's been a brother on a
different team now come again and we be
brothers again on the same team. So,
>> Right. Right.
>> How do how does a player like that on in
front of you help just make your life so
much easier on the back end?
>> It's so good. It's it makes so much
difference because you know there could
be a play where maybe you're not in the
best position and then the ball don't
come in the sky and you look back and
it's like Trey going like this got a
sack you know it's like oh okay bet like
okay like I don't have to be perfect you
know what I'm saying so like you know
you always need guys like that that can
like you know cover mistakes and also
just you know take over a game third
downs fourth downs important downs
>> fourth quarter two-minute drill all
those times like they come alive you
know like those sacks matter matter like
like you know second second down sacks
first down sacks like okay that's that's
good it pushes them back but like when
they matter like that's what I've
experienced at least playing with Trey
Hendrickson it's like he gets sacks when
they matter and he'll take over a game I
remember one two-minute drill we were um
in practice when I was on Cincinnati
>> and um it was a long practice one of
those like you know dog days of camp
>> and we had a two-minute drill at the end
of practice we're going against the ones
and we're like Trey end this for us bro
like we don't want we don't want to he
got a back three straight plays. Boom.
First, second down, second down. First
down, second down, third down. Then the
drill was over. Like bet. Like we're
chilling now, you know? But like that's
the type of player he is. So yeah,
>> that's awesome. Well, you talk about
taking over games, man. I remember uh in
Minnesota, Justin Jefferson.
>> You
I mean, you had a game that that was a
hell of a game, man. So looking forward
to more of that. Garrett and I we we do
have to pat ourselves on the back.
Before you resigned, we were like, we
want to get Cheeto done. We're talking
about like offseason priorities. We were
like, "We want to see Cheeto return."
>> Did you feel like it was it was a
foregone conclusion or did you think
that you could have go elsewhere? Like
what?
>> I had no idea honestly this year I I
like kind of just sat back and just was
like, I'm going to take it as it comes.
>> Um I feel like I've been through it a
couple times and you know, you could be
stressed out or you could be like, okay,
what's going to happen or like who's
going to do all this stuff. But it's
like this time I was, you know, I didn't
show my process. I was still training.
my sister um had like her traditional
engagement so to say this past weekend.
So I was focused on that. Um so yeah, I
was chilling and then you know obviously
when the opportunity you know looked
more real I was like of course you know
um and I was excited. So I don't think I
would want to be anywhere else.
>> Well big thanks to Cheto for joining the
lounge. You were listening to the lounge
podcast. We're coming to you from the
seat geek studio. We want to mention our
partners at DraftKings Sportsbook. They
are an official sports betting partner
of the Baltimore Ravens. DraftKings
Sportsbook, the crown is yours. So, busy
day for the Ravens. Cheetah was one of
five guys who signed his contract here
today as free agency. Really took off
for the Ravens today in terms of the
official pen to paper. He was one. Trey
Hendrickson was the other big one. Uh
the Ravens officially signed him to his
four-year contract. So, it's exciting to
have Trey Hendrickson here. Uh but it
wasn't just them. John Simpson back in
the building, left guard, uh signs his
contract. Uh Durham Smi, tight end, uh
formerly of the Chicago Bears, also
signs his contract. and Jaylen Hawkins,
safety uh from the New England Patriots.
All five of them here signed their
contracts and are officially Ravens.
>> Yeah, it's an exciting day when uh when
Penn is put to paper. And so I think
that this Ravens free agency has been a
a wild ride and there's been some
unexpected twists and turns,
>> but when you have a day like this, it
gives you the the uh good vibes coming
out the other side of that to say like,
"Oh man, like I really like these guys
that Baltimore added." And and of
course, day one is always a difficult
day. Monday was a difficult day. When
you have so many departures, you know,
seven departures on the first day, it's
it's tough. Uh but then you you start to
make some additions, right? And the
whole Max Crosby thing, that was a whole
wild turn. But you get to this point
right now, and I I like what the Ravens
have done, uh bringing in these five
guys and and bringing back, you know,
Cheeto obviously. And so I I think it's
a very good day here in Baltimore. Yeah,
I think that if you would just if you
kind of fast forward to today and you
skipped six days prior and like the
roller coaster of the Max Crosby
situation and the departure, like if you
just knew that on the horizon here,
you're getting Trey Hendrickson,
Cheetah's coming back, like you're
getting these additions. Here's the
crazy part about Trey Hendrickson uh
specifically is
>> if the Ravens had just gone out and not
pursued Max Crosby at all and not made a
trade
>> and you told Ravens fans we just landed
Trey Hendrickson, the top free agent
available on the market at a huge
position of need for the Ravens, we'd
all be ecstatic
>> and we are. We are now. But the whole
thing just got thrown off by the whole
Max Crosby situation and the possibility
that we could have had both guys and and
all that and and it it made for a wonky
kind of experience.
>> Yeah.
>> Now you have Trey Hendrickson in the
building here today and you see him and
you see how excited he is and happy he
is and and you're like, "Yeah, man. Just
got Trey Hendrickson.
>> We got Trey Hendrickson." You know what
I mean? This guy that's terrorized our
quarterbacks for so many years. And so
it's awesome.
>> I loved hearing what Cheeto had to say
about playing alongside. I mean, don't
forget these two guys went to a Super
Bowl together when they were with the
Cincinnati Bengals. And you can tell and
hearing from him that he's excited to
team up again that those two guys were
critical pieces on that Cincinnati
defense. And Hendrickson just has that
kind of he's a differencemaker. He's a
he's a differencemaker. The the point
that Cheeto made that stood out to me
about Trey is him being a closer
>> and that's what the Ravens have needed.
Not only have you just needed sacks,
right? The Ravens finished tied for the
third fewest in the league last year.
So, they needed to get more pressure and
sacks overall, but they've need needed
closers because there's been too many
fourth quarter meltdowns defensively
over the last number of years here. And
you look around the league a lot of
times what closes out games and doesn't
allow teams to come back on you is when
they're in pass heavy mode and they got
to chuck the ball and you got somebody
on your side who can take down the
quarterback and put them in third and 20
right when it's Hail Mary prayer time.
And that's that's what Trey Hendrickson
has shown himself to be over the years.
And I think that's who he's going to be
here in Baltimore. And and and that is a
that is a really big deal.
>> Yeah. I I totally agree. And and
speaking to Cheeto, look, you and I have
both been fans of him and what he
brings. Uh and I think that getting him
back on a on a one-year, $5 million
contract is is a great move for the
Ravens.
>> I thought he could I thought after the
year that he had last season that there
was the potential that he could parlay
that into a two even maybe a three-year
deal and and, you know, could be
departing, you know, and and I so I
think it's a it's a really great thing
for both sides and it's a pay bump for
Cheeto. you know, he kind of was on a
prove it deal last year this time after
struggling with injuries and all that
and and he proved it. You know, he had a
great season. So, I think it works out
well for both sides.
>> Yeah. And and like $5 million for a
starting quarterback is is great market
value for the Ravens. And
>> it's not as good as $5, but it's good.
>> Yeah, exactly. It's not $5, but it's not
bad. But yeah, he's he's like he's going
to play a lot of snaps for this team.
He's going to start games and he's going
to play a huge role and and he said it
off the top that just feels like there's
unfinished business. Not happy with the
way that the season ended as a team
individually and just feels like he's
motivated uh to to get back to work and
try to to take help this team to the
next step. I liked what he said about
the energy that he felt in the building
with new coaching staff and and just
feeling that togetherness, that
connectedness that Jesse Menter talked
about in his introductory press
conference that it was going to be a
tenant of of his tenure here in
Baltimore. and and it was neat to hear
Cheeto already feeling that and and
talking about it and how he feels like,
you know, this this DB room and the and
the defense as a whole is going to be
just so together and playing for each
other and playing for the bigger cause
and and those kind of things. So that's
really exciting because you you forget
man there, you know, beyond the free
agency losses and additions, so many on
the coaching side. So, this is one, it's
just been a an off seasonason of
turnover and so everybody's going to
kind of get to know everybody. There's
fresh races all over the place and uh
it's going to be really neat and um
>> an interesting experience this summer as
that all that kind of gels.
>> Yeah, you can feel the there's
definitely an energy and and today was
an example of that. You have these guys
here, they sign their contracts, they're
meeting the new coaches and it it kind
of starts to feel like all right, the
the team is coming together. there's a
building process moving towards the
season and that that got me excited and
I think Ravens fans certainly should be
fired up about what's to come.
>> Couple moves that we talk about uh you
know as we continue to break down what's
going down in free agency. Katon
Mitchell has reportedly signed a
two-year deal to go out with the LA
Chargers and so congrats to Katon.
>> Ravens West continues.
>> Ravens West Joe Ortiz man he he those
ties that they run deep. Uh,
>> Joe, long time friend of the lounge.
Just taking some of our favorite guys.
>> What's up, Joe?
>> Yeah,
>> we love, you know, he's still a loyal
viewer, I'm sure.
>> Oh, I'm sure he's still watching. So,
uh, you know, hey, wish Keaton all the
luck, uh, out there, except, you know,
if they go toe-to-toe with us. So,
>> I mean, nice contract for him. Uh,
two-year, $10 million contract almost.
And so, like, this is a guy, undrafted
player, then has a devastating,
devastating knee injury as a rookie. as
Katon had said to us at the time, some
of the people that he talked to felt
like, yeah, he may never get on the
field again, right? And so for him to
work his way back and then not just play
again, but play at a high level and
prove himself and then get a contract,
he's he's been a guy that I've really
like, so I don't like seeing him leave.
But I do he he's somebody who I think is
easy to root for, and I'm happy to see
him get that contract and get an
opportunity to play on that offense.
>> Yep. And then the Ravens uh have
reportedly agreed to a one-year deal
with guard/c center Javon Gwyn. So uh
interior line depth. He played with the
Atlanta Falcons uh previously. So coming
over here with coach Leadford and
obviously a lot of good intel there. And
Eric Tasa said yesterday that the Ravens
could very well be in the V veteran
center market. And so, you know, Javon's
not a guy who has a ton of starting
experience, uh, or really any, but I
think a good depth piece and he can
compete compete for the job.
>> I think it's depth and it's competition.
>> Exactly.
>> And when you're looking at that interior
of the offensive line, especially after
the departure of Tyler Linderbomb, you
want both of those things
>> and familiarity. You know,
>> he knows the system.
>> He knows Yeah. what coach Leadford wants
to run and coach Leadford knows him and
what you know that's sometimes when
you're trying to find a little bit of a
diamond in the rough you know hey I I'll
vouch for this guy I know what he's
capable of doing even though the rest of
the league hasn't really seen it on tape
>> very similar situation to Durham Smith
the veteran blocking tight end who the
Ravens sign who played last year with
the Bears where Declan Doyle was the
offensive coordinator
>> it's fun seeing some of these new
coaches pluck some of their guys
>> yeah we've seen it we've seen guys going
up to New York to play with Harbaugh
guys going out west to play for
to steal some.
>> Now, now we're getting in on the action.
Um, and and look, on Friday, we're going
to get a chance to hear from Tre
Hendrickson. Uh, he's going to meet with
reporters during a press conference
Friday morning, 10:00 a.m. And you'll be
able to watch that on our app, our
website, uh, YouTube channel. We're
going to stream it for you live. So,
it'll be fun to talk with Trey a little
bit more, get a sense of his excitement
to be here in Baltimore and and then
seeing him here today. There's
definitely energy that he has uh, coming
here and joining this defense. So, make
sure you check out that full press
conference. uh tomorrow, Friday, 10:00
a.m. And uh we're going to continue to
break down everything over the course of
free agency. Thank you so much for
listening and watching. We'll be back
with you again soon.